const LiterarySources = [
	{
		questionText: 'ప్రతాపరుద్ర యశోభూషణం/ప్రతాపరుద్రియమ్',
		ans: ['విద్యనాథుడు', 'Sanskrit'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'పురుషార్ధసారం',
		ans: ['శివదేవయ్య'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'క్రీడాభిరామం',
		ans: ['వినుకొండ వల్లభ'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'శివయోగసారం',
		ans: ['కొలను గణపతిదేవుడు'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'ప్రతాప చరిత్ర',
		ans: ['ఏకామ్రనాథ', 'Telugu'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'నీతిసారం',
		ans: ['రుద్రదేవుడు'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'నీతిశాస్త్ర ముక్తావళి',
		ans: ['బద్దెన'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'నృత్య రత్నావళి',
		ans: ['జయప్ప సేనాని'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'పండితారాద్య చరిత్ర',
		ans: ['పాల్కురికి సోమనాథ'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'సిద్దేశ్వర చరిత్ర',
		ans: ['కాసే సర్వప్ప'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'రంగనాథ రామాయణం',
		ans: ['గోనబుడ్డ రెడ్డి'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'ఆంధ్ర మహాభారతం',
		ans: ['తిక్కన్న సోమయాజి'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'పల్నాటి వీర చరిత్ర',
		ans: ['శ్రీనాథుడు'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'fatus-us-kashueni',
		ans: ['Amir khushro'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Fatu-us-salatin',
		ans: ['ఇసామి'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'The Travels ',
		ans: ['Mark Polo'],
	},
	// {
	// 	questionText: '',
	// 	ans: [''],
	// },

];

export default LiterarySources;
